{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " The tower of Babel was built out of? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Bricks and cement"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Stone and mortar"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Stone and tar"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Bricks and tar"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Bricks and tar",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " By confusing their language all of the following resulted at Babel EXCEPT",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. People were scattered over the face of the earth "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. People of different languages fought each other "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. People stopped building the tower "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. People could not understand each other "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " b. People of different languages fought each other ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Prior to the tower of Babel, what did the whole world have in common?  ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Sacrificing to angels "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Lived in one city "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. One language "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. One food source "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. One language ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did humankind build the tower of Babel?    ",
      "time": "13000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. So that they would not be scattered over the earth "
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. So that they could worship their own gods "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. So that they could become like God "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. So that a flood would never destroy everyone again "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. So that they would not be scattered over the earth ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who was Abram's father ? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Shelah "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Nahor "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Peleg "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Terah"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Terah",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who was the wife of Abraham ? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Sarah"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Rebekah"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Leah"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Rachel"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Sarah",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Abraham a descendant of which of Noahâ€™s three sons? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Ham "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b Japheth "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Shem "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Canaan "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Shem ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Abraham moved with his father and family, to what city where his father     died?",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Babylon "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Nineveh "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Jerusalem "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Haran "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Haran ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Abraham was Lot's _________?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Grandfather "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Uncle "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Nephew "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Cousin "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Uncle ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did Abraham originally move from?  ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Jerusalem"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Nineveh of the Assyrians "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Ur of the Chaldees "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Babylon of the Akkadians  "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Ur of the Chaldees ",
      "type": "epi_6"
    }
  ]
}